Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
Go back to Mama!
Good morning, Jesmark.
Morning, ma’am.
Catch any fish today?
No, nothing.
You always catch something.
- Just one.
- One.
C’mon, not the big one.
Do I get the special price?
Fine, the special price.
Bye, Jesmark.
Carry on.
A fish for every girl?
So many girls, so few fish.
- What’s wrong?
- Dunno.
Looks okay here.
Easy, you’re gonna bust it.
Yeah, but...
Here’s your problem.
I’ll redo the caulking.
Caulking won’t fix it.
The boat itself
has a structural problem.
Your dad used to break his back
on this luzzu.
Yeah, I remember.
C’mon, let’s pull it up.
- Watch your driving!
- You chose this road.
Oh, it’s my fault?
If it’s full of potholes,
what can I do?
You love driving through them.
You haven’t missed
a single one yet.
Should I drive backwards?
That’s enough!
- Here’s fine, right?
- Of course.
One, two...
Slowly.
One more.
Let’s do it right.
- You got it in there?
- Yeah.
Let it dry,
then we’ll get started.
We’ll make it good as new.
You’ll be out in force-10 winds.
Not even God will stop it!
C’mon, let’s go.
Easy!
Coming.
I said I’m coming!
- I know I’m late. Sorry Mary Grace.
- I called you.
- Didn’t hear your phone?
- My battery died.
Yeah, right, it was ringing.
You didn’t pick up.
Here.
You’re the best, Mary Grace!
Yeah, Prince Charming.
Hey, Denise said you’d pay me.
The money’s upstairs.
I’ll bring it later.
- Don’t keep me waiting.
- I won’t, I’ll bring it.
Jesmark!
I’m late!
Yes!
Alright I’m here.
Where are you?
Behind you.
Hey!
What happened?
- The luzzu’s got a leak.
- Again?
Hey, handsome.
C’mon, let’s make a move.
You smell like a whale’s pussy.
Yeah, I know.
See the bunny?
Did you see the bunny?
And the blocks?
- We’ve got something for you.
- What?
Yuck, Jes’!
It’s not my fault.
He gets that from you, not me.
You sure?
Yes, I’m sure.
Aiden Saliba, please.
C’mon, that’s us.
See what she’s doing?
The doctor better see me instead.
- I have witnesses.
- Oh, poor you.
There, good boy.
Are you eating well, Denise?
- What, can’t you tell?
- Hey!
- Isn’t it true?
- Yes, I’m eating fine.
I’m sorry to ask,
but are you smoking or drinking?
No.
And you’re back at work, now?
And you, Jesmark.
How long do you stay at sea?
A day or two.
- Who takes care of Aiden?
- Our neighbour.
So...
It’s hard to say what’s causing it.
Maybe it’s something genetic.
In the family, that is.
Or his environment.
His environment?
We don’t know exactly but
Aiden isn’t growing properly and
we need to do something immediately.
Now, here’s what we’ll do.
We’ll start a diet
with a fattening formula.
You’ll need to take him
to a dietician once a week.
I’d also like you to see
a speech therapist.
A speech therapist?
To see if it’s a problem
with his swallowing.
And we can do this here?
No, he needs specialists.
Otherwise, you risk him
not developing properly.
I’m up all night feeding him.
He is eating.
I know, Denise.
These things happen.
What things?
For example, sometimes mothers
don’t produce enough milk.
Sometimes the baby doesn’t
accept it.
- Doesn’t accept it?
- So it’s my fault?
- No, that’s not what I’m saying.
- Yes, you are.
Alright, it’s not my fault then.
If it’s not our fault, whose is it?
Hey, come back.
I’m sorry.
Don’t worry,
I’ve seen cases like this.
But right now it’s critical...
Feed him well and get him
the care he needs.
This one?
That’s the normal kind.
We need this.
That’s more fattening.
Fifty and two cents, please.
Here, Jes’.
C’mon, don’t worry.
That’s it, little jellyfish.
He seems to like it.
For 40 euros, I’d hope so.
There’s quite a few
seabream this year.
If this keeps up,
should be a good season.
Do you know how much
it’s going to cost us?
The immunizations alone
are 300 euros.
You think I don’t know?
I saw someone post this.
Trawlers destroy the seabed.
Sorry, I can’t do that.
So what are we going to do, Jes’?
We’ll find a specialist we can afford.
I already called my mum.
Why drag her into this?
Half her friends are doctors.
She brags about it enough.
C’mon, Jes’.
Weren’t you the one who didn’t
want her around?
She broke her promise
for your tattoo shop.
She wants you under her thumb.
I know.
Why are you giving in now?
I’ll take care of us, okay?
It’s time.
Throw it, throw it!
You’re gonna tear my finger off!
We’ll catch a big fish with it.
We’d be done already
if you set the lines properly.
When you fix your luzzu,
set up the lines
however you want.
Anything?
Not a bite. Dunno why.
Here we go!
Take the line to the prow.
We’ve got something for sure!
Don’t send me up here for
nothing.
Get the hook!
Hurry, hurry!
C’mon!
Grab him by the head.
Fucking swordfish.
Chuck it, let’s make a move!
What are you doing?
We’re keeping it.
C’mon, in closed season?
And so what?
It’s worth 500 euros for sure.
Hey, close that hatch!
- Why?
- My boat, my risk.
Forget closed season,
you know it’s bullshit.
It’s illegal.
They’ll screw me.
Since when has it been illegal?
Since when?
We’ve been fishing like this
for a thousand years.
It’s dead! What will you get
by throwing it back?
Don’t get me into trouble.
You know what’s happening
with Aiden. I need this.
- Give me a chance, okay?
- Don’t be a pain in the ass!
What are you doing?
Think everyone else is a saint?
Fisheries?
This is the Kolarosa.
Listen, we were bottom fishing
and caught a swordfish on the line.
That’s right, a swordfish.
Yes, okay, but...
Can’t we sort something out?
These things die the minute
you take them out of the water.
Can’t we keep it
for ourselves at least?
For our families?
- Move.
- You fucked it.
Good morning.
Morning.
What do we have?
Three boxes.
- This is everything?
- That’s it.
- Let’s see your logbook.
- Grab it, Jesmark.
Let’s see.
A box of snappers, skate,
and dogfish.
- I need to do an inspection.
- Are you serious?
All boats require routine
checks.
So do my balls.
Drop it, let’s get on with it.
If your boat is clean,
this will be quick.
What’s he looking for?
His mother?
Watch your mouth.
Next time, I’ll cite you.
Cite whatever the fuck you want.
Have a good day.
Can you shut your mouth for
once?
Shut my mouth?
C’mon, man. Next time,
he’ll really screw us.
Next time, I’ll knock him
into the sea.
Careful, box behind you.
They never sell our stuff
till the end, see?
Who’s this new hawker?
The new owners brought him in.
Five for lampuki.
- You’re free to go elsewhere!
- Give us a good price!
Give us a deal!
Squid: five sixty.
Write that down.
There’s our fish. Let’s go.
Last fish of the day! Last fish!
Dogfish and skate!
Skate, one fifty!
What the hell is he doing?
Dogfish, four euros!
Sell our snappers!
Stop wasting time
with the fucking dogfish!
Dogfish, four euros!
You need to sell our good stuff!
Wanna sell? Do it yourself!
- Come on, man!
- What the hell!
Come back! You can’t do that!
You taking it or not?
We don’t have anywhere
to keep them.
- We don’t have a freezer van!
- Better sell quick! C’mon!
Take it.
Fucking bastard.
- Morning.
- What’s up?
- Interested in anything today?
- Depends on what you have.
My fridge is full.
Take some of mine, too.
For tomorrow.
See how fresh it looks?
I’ve still got leftovers.
- This is fresh.
- I’ve got leftovers.
- You don’t want this one?
- Too small.
- Small?
- Yeah, small. C’mon.
- How much for it?
- Fourteen.
C’mon, they used to be 15.
Don’t I deserve 15?
A fisherman came before you.
How much did you get?
Come back tomorrow.
Thank you.
I said don’t come here.
- That wasn’t my fault!
- Take your stuff and leave.
Don’t show your face
around here anymore.
We can’t keep going on like
this.
That’s all I’ve got.
Alright?
- I told you not to...
- I know.
- Please don’t.
- Why?
Can’t you let me try?
You know my brother
and nephews fish for me.
Yeah, they catch good stuff.
But this is better.
What did I just tell you?
I’ll have to throw it out.
The garbage is outside.
If he comes again,
it’ll be bad for him
and worse for you.
He didn’t take them?
Onto the next, let’s go.
They’re starting to stink.
Let’s just throw them out.
Make the sign of the cross,
friend.
God, bless this fisherman’s boat.
Deliver them from danger,
fill their nets,
and bring them home safely.
Gianni? What happened to him?
Poor Gianni ended up
in that shit show.
- Is that still going on?
- The laws are too strict.
It’s like this slipway.
They fixed the wooden slats,
but you can’t use it
or you’ll get fined.
Back in the day,
luzzus could come and go.
- Nowadays, they’re not practical.
- Exactly.
They’re fixing them with European funds
and we don’t even get to use them.
Laws, laws, don’t you remember
my uncle?
Yeah, poor Sammy.
He went to work in a factory
and he was losing his mind.
Then he borrowed money
to buy a tuna quota,
but no tuna came that season.
So what did he do?
They caught him
with contraband cigarettes.
Two years jail, three years probation,
and 100,000 euro fine.
- Tell me who will pay for that?
- His children.
- It’s like we’re criminals.
- That how it is, now.
And you?
What happened to the luzzu?
Pulled it up on the beach.
But the wood will shrink like that.
I know, but it was going to sink.
- It’s better in the sea than on land.
- I’m gonna fix it.
I’m gonna fix it.
Yeah, but wood isn’t fiberglass.
Wood is a living thing.
Now I’ll see where it needs
caulking.
I’ll sand the whole thing
down to the waterline.
Should take about a week.
Don’t scratch it,
you’ll only add more work.
Change this whole piece.
That’s the one that’s been
giving me trouble.
Just have to find someone
to do the job.
A final lick of paint...
Antifouling and we’re ready to go.
- And if it leaks again?
- It won’t.
I’ll use a good sealant. The new piece
will be custom-built.
It won’t leak.
I promise.
Let’s get Aiden before
Mary Grace starts calling.
He’s not with Mary Grace.
Where is he?
Mum picked him up this morning.
Why?
She offered.
We need help.
We’re fine.
Where are you going?
To my mum’s.
She booked doctor appointments
for tomorrow.
You didn’t tell me.
Should we meet there?
No, don’t worry.
I’ll take care of everything.
He’s my son, too.
Do you think it was easy
for me to call her?
C’mon, I’ll drive you.
I can manage.
It’ll take you forever on the bus.
I’m telling you,
it was the biggest catch of his life.
Didn’t you ever hear this?
Picture this...
The luzzu is full of lampuki...
Engine’s totally fucked...
And with incredible strength,
your dad rowed
all the way back to shore.
Jesus, these rips are huge.
Don’t make a fuss.
Just clean them.
What will you catch with these?
Whales?
Watch out, Cikas.
Move, Cikas.
Mind if I crash here tonight?
You can sleep with Cikas
on his cushion.
Tomorrow?
We have appointments all day again.
So what’s the plan?
Give me the rest of the week here.
Can I bring you guys anything?
We’re okay.
Is he with you?
He’s right here.
Let me listen.
Jesmark...
Is Denise here?
I tried calling her.
She went to see her uncle.
Here.
- This will give him gas.
- How do you know?
Doctor’s orders, not mine.
You can’t feed him this cheap stuff.
Is Aiden here?
He’s asleep.
Can I see him?
I just put him down.
He didn’t sleep much.
I’d like to see him.
Please.
Hey, handsome.
Alright, monkey?
Here, take this one.
It’s always nice to see you.
Did I say I was leaving?
Make an offer!
Is this fucking guy serious?
Sell it at four euros!
Didn’t you sell the others at four?
Auction is over.
I saw the swordfish.
I don’t know
what you’re talking about.
What the fuck are you doing here?
- You got trouble?
- It’s not your business, man.
Let me talk to your boss.
Why, you got scallops?
Scallops?
Boss needs scallops.
You got them?
No?
Then get the fuck out of here!
We don’t need you.
Move, man!
Don’t waste our time.
C’mon, move!
Keep moving, man! Fuck off!
My trucks are loaded.
We have an understanding.
They’re on their way.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
- You can make money off these.
Cook ’em,
no one will know the difference.
- How much?
- Fifty.
You’re kidding me, right?
You come in here
and try to sell my junk back to me?
It’s not junk if you know
what you’re doing.
Don’t tell me you’ve been
selling these off for cat food.
I get good prices.
Let me work with you.
You’ll see what I can do.
- Can you clean a fish?
- In my sleep.
- What do you pay?
- One fifty.
Two hundred and your trucks
make it on time.
Later.
Turn it more so it doesn’t
get swept away.
It’s safe here.
I don’t think you remember
because you’re young.
Your grandfather set out with
this boat,
going with the eastern wind,
the "foreign chill."
Clouds were gathering in the west
and your grandfather saw it coming.
The wind was merciless.
He wasn’t going to make it.
Then a big ship came towards him.
He kept close to that ship
all night for shelter.
And by morning,
he said he’d arrived in Tunis.
Sicily maybe!
You need two days for Tunis!
That’s your grandfather’s story.
Yeah, a story for the gullible!
What can I do for you?
- Got time?
- Which side?
Right.
- That’s 40 inches.
- That’s right.
Very good.
How’s that?
Can you leave it for now?
I’ll come back later.
- What’s wrong?
- Nothing.
- Don’t make me work for nothing.
- Of course not.
- You’re coming back for it, right?
- Of course.
What’s wrong?
- Do you need petrol?
- What?
- Do you want petrol?
- Petrol?
For your car.
- Is it mixed with something?
- Of course not.
- Will it damage the engine?
- No, it won’t. C’mon.
Want some?
How much?
- 30 euros a can?
- For that much, I’ll go to the station.
It’ll be more at the station.
Okay, how much?
Twenty-five?
Alright?
- Anything extra for me?
- You don’t deserve shit.
- It’s clean, right?
- I was using it myself.
- I have more over there.
- Gentleman’s word?
Nothing to worry about.
Jes’!
Hey, Kev’!
Alright, man?
What’s with the shirt?
Carla’s idea.
You know how she is.
Throw it in the dumpster.
What’s all this?
- Need some?
- No, tank’s full.
Fucking 60 euros to fill a tank now.
Bye-bye subsidy.
What happened?
Didn’t you hear?
Hear what?
I’m not fishing anymore.
I took the EU buyout deal.
Turned in my boat and licence.
I didn’t know.
It’s been a few months.
I should get back to work.
Hey, I’ll take one.
Isn’t your tank full?
I’ll need it later.
Don’t worry, I’ll sell it.
I should try to beat the traffic.
Good to see you.
So what do they need to do now?
Well...
It’s up to us now.
We have to be sure
he keeps gaining.
I got a new job.
I’m quitting at Lino’s.
A new job?
You didn’t tell me.
My uncle sorted it out this week...
at the Planning Agency.
So your uncle’s good now?
You said he’s a crook.
He’s only trying to help.
You’ll rubber stamp
some permits for him?
I’ll be doing graphic design.
One of us needs a good job.
I know you love what you do.
We don’t look at work the same way.
I don’t want him to have less
than what I had.
- I don’t want him...
- To be like me?
You know that’s not what I think.
And your family?
C’mon, Jes’.
Am I gonna do the whole thing myself?
Without a boat...
You lose your way.
I’ve seen it happen to other guys.
If your dad was here...
Can you stop?
What?
Think I don’t know what he’d say?
I know what I have to do.
I’m off.
Check out the nerve of this guy.
The waypoints are marked.
Uday will show you the rest.
Welcome aboard, fisherman.
Have coffee.
This your boat?
My boat?
This is my Titanic.
My home, brother.
Sea workers like me travel the world,
just for the work.
They don’t give permissions
to live on the land.
So we live on the boats.
- I’ve never left this island.
- Never?
A fish stays in the bowl...
Never grows.
Can you see it?
That’s it, that’s the one!
To the right.
See?
This is the marker.
When a fisherman catches a fish,
which he isn’t supposed to catch,
he throws it back into the sea and
marks the spot so that we can find it.
You have to be fast though,
while it’s fresh.
We give it to the boss,
he sells it.
Fisherman gets a cut, too.
Which fishermen?
Could be anyone.
Your friends, even.
You know how many fucking fish
I’ve thrown in the sea?
Give me the rope.
C’mon, man. Keep it moving.
Got anything else?
Like what?
Anything.
How much do we have in the back?
With us?
It’s nothing, brother.
Maybe a couple thousand.
We’ve done bigger deals.
Restaurants, fish shops.
They pay huge amounts
when it’s closed season.
They buy fresh from us...
Or frozen from the supermarkets.
I saw your boss pay the
inspector.
He’s a big fish, too?
You got it, brother.
This is my favourite song, man.
We got money in the back, c’mon!
C’mon! What the fuck, man?
Dance with me!
I love it.
This is my shit.
Did he sleep much?
I just put him down.
I saw David’s boat on the dock.
You didn’t go with him?
No, I didn’t.
So you went with Tonio?
I took a shift on the trawler.
Can you get more work with them?
Yeah.
He’ll need to eat soon.
- We have formula?
- Everything’s in the kitchen.
Alright.
- Gotta run. You’ll be okay?
- I’ll take care of everything.
I’m off.
Hey, man, wait a second.
I got it for you.
Be careful, huh?
You called me for a box of fish?
Say thank you, brother.
This is an opportunity.
The boss needs favors from politicians.
But they don’t like brown guys.
Especially their cash in my hands.
You know?
Better get moving.
And don’t fuck up.
You’re the new guy?
See you.
I need guys to move my stuff.
Salmon in...
Tuna out.
You got a freezer van?
Freezer van?
Like this.
Think I got that kind of money?
Don’t you need more fishermen?
Jesus Christ.
How many fish do you think
will be left in 20 years?
The way the temperature is rising?
Don’t read much, do you?
Better start.
Your family?
Yes, mother and sister.
Miss them?
My sister is coming soon.
Boss is helping with it.
We got her a place to live.
We got her into a nursing school.
This guy’s got friends
everywhere.
If you keep working with us,
he’ll help you, too.
I love this food.
The taste is nice.
Yeah, really nice.
It’s the spice.
What do you mean?
Those fishermen,
they make trouble to us.
We pay them back.
That’s part of our job.
People who fuck with us,
we fuck with them.
That’s it.
Hey man, let’s go!
Hurry up!
Hurry up, man!
Let’s go, man. Hurry up!
Come have a look.
Finished the caulking.
Called in a favor
for the missing piece.
All that’s left now
is painting the rest,
antifouling,
and in a couple of days
it’s ready to go.
See?
What do you think?
Proper job, no?
- What do I owe you?
- Don’t worry, man.
Let me at least
pay for the materials.
Tell me what I owe you.
Can you spot me
for the expenses?
My nets got damaged
a couple days ago.
Someone slashed them.
Yours too?
- Heard anything about it?
- The others were talking but...
- Yeah, they screwed us all.
- The work you did here is great.
- Pretty good, huh?
- You can hardly tell.
Now you have a brand new luzzu.
Strong as ever.
Hey there, little sailor.
I just need your signature now.
What do you think, boss?
Shall we do it, Jes’?
Take off his sock for me.
Come here, little jellyfish.
Turn his foot around.
He’s ticklish.
Let’s do it here.
Like the other one.
Quick, before the paint dries.
Wow, it came out really good!
Your feet were bigger at his age.
One hundred days old, already?
They grow fast, don’t they?
I’ve been meaning to ask you...
Did you eat pears when
you were pregnant with Aiden?
Don’t think so.
Pears are a huge problem for boys.
- Did she actually say pears?
- Yes, of course, pears!
If you had asked your mum,
she’d have told you.
Pears are sandy in texture.
It causes problems when they pee.
Only boys.
Maybe that’s Aiden’s problem.
- Maybe.
- Ask her.
How long till this is over?
C’mon, it won’t kill you.
- The furniture shop?
- That’s right.
Listen, if you ever need a job...
they’re always looking for movers.
Movers?
Movers are people like you.
Strong.
Men that can carry furniture.
First one, go ahead.
Wow, how cute.
Look at this Jes’, how cute.
These will keep him warm,
the sole is leather.
You can tell.
They look really sweet!
Time for the big one.
Look at the quality.
- Who’s this from?
- From me.
- I hope you like it.
- Sure.
It matches the one we have.
I can swap it if you want.
Swap it? There’s no need.
We’d know these things if you
hadn’t buried your heads in the sand.
- Come on.
- Isn’t it true?
We don’t know how
you two are living.
Maybe we like the sand.
- No one likes sand.
- What are we even talking about?
I think the sand is a metaphor.
When you were young,
it was okay to just take off.
- Who’s taking off?
- Jes’!
Cruising on the boat everyday,
barbecues in the evening.
Sell a fish every now and then.
Do you ever think about your son?
- Let’s drop it.
- No, let her tell us.
Come on, enlighten us.
Fishing is a nice way
to waste a summer.
This is a nice way
to waste a life.
Sometimes they disagree
with the mother-in-law.
They’re young.
He’ll see things my way.
Mark my words.
Best to stay quiet and say nothing.
You can’t not give them advice.
Anyway, let’s open the rest.
I’ll open it instead of them.
Leave it.
- Leave it!
- Why?
We’re gonna go through this
again?
Look, I don’t expect you to change.
I’ve made it so you can be like this.
Like what?
The only reason you can still fish
is because of those people out there.
- This about the job with your uncle?
- Not just the job.
Who knows how many times we barely
have enough money for rent.
Bill after bill comes in,
we don’t have cash,
and then suddenly,
money magically appears.
What are you saying?
Where do you think
that money comes from?
Do you want him
to grow up like you?
Go get him.
Can you get him so we can leave?
Aiden and I are staying.
Again?
When there’s a problem,
you run to your mother.
I can’t do that.
I have to solve my problems myself.
Tell me the truth...
Did you ever believe
you and I would make it?
Another holiday at your mum’s?
Maybe I’ll get used to it.
Fisheries and Sea Authority
Name?
Jesmark Saliba.
Your boat’s name.
Ta’ Palma.
- That’s an old luzzu.
- Yeah.
Length?
Twelve footer.
Material?
Wood, obviously.
Your licence?
Trammel nets and long lines.
How old is it?
Dunno.
If you had to take a guess?
It was my dad’s, my grandfather’s,
my great-grandfather’s...
Okay, that’s enough.
"Permanent Cessation
of Fishing Activities"
Do you understand what that means?
The financing for this program
comes from the European Union.
The goal is to reduce the fishing fleet
and move fishermen
into other industries.
Now, according to the
information here,
we come up with an estimate
for your compensation.
How much is it?
You need to decommission
the luzzu first
before we can complete
this application.
Do you understand?
Just tell me how much.
Seven thousand.
You won’t even get ten percent
of that selling it online.
As I told you,
take a training program.
Make an investment.
It’s up to you.
Listen, my friend.
When you decide what you’re
going to do, give me a call.
Next!
Look, it’s Jesmark!
- Is it ready yet?
- Yeah, it’s ready.
Let’s have a blessing then.
- Don’t go out of your way.
- It’ll only take a minute.
- Another time, thanks anyway.
- Now that it’s fixed up?
Come, I’ll bless it.
God, bless this fisherman’s boat.
Deliver him from danger.
Fill his nets,
and return him home safely.
Grab it, Jes’.
Let’s have a look.
See what a nice job
I’ve done for you?
That silicone caulking
works wonders, huh?
Not a drop of water coming in.
Happy?
Yes.
Jesmark Saliba.
Tomorrow.
All good?
Yeah, except for your shirt.
Carla...
You got it from here?
- Ready?
- Yeah, I got it.
Hey.
No worries, right?
Thanks, man.
- Fishing licence and chain of title.
- Did you remove the engine?
Yes.
- Gearbox and the rest?
- Everything’s ready.
Good.
Good luck.
What name do you give your child?
- Aiden.
What do you wish for Aiden?
- Eternal life.
You have asked for your
child to be baptized.
You will raise your son
in the faith of the Church
to follow the commandments,
and to love God and his neighbor
as Christ taught us.
Do you understand
what you are undertaking?
- We do.
Let us pray to our Lord Almighty,
to let this child be reborn
in water and the Holy Spirit.
Aiden...
I baptize you
in the name of the Father,
the Son,
and the Holy Spirit.
Take some photos of them.
Squeeze in, let me take a photo.
A bit more.
Jesmark...
Jesmark, one minute here, please.
And turn the baby around.
Hold, hold.
Give me a second.
Aiden’s here.
- Is that good?
- Average, as he should be.
Now is one of the most exciting stages.
He’ll begin recognising your voices,
making eye contact.
We call this stage "hatching."
Even his personality starts to
develop.
Everything around Aiden will affect him,
including who you are as individuals.
Do you ever talk to him,
Jesmark?
Talk to him?
Tell him a story,
even if it’s something simple.
Talk about your day,
what you’re doing.
It’s important to talk to him.
It’ll help him develop
his language skills later on...
- Is the freezer okay?
- Fixed. Better than it ever was.
Good.
- You could have washed it.
- It costs extra for that.
Take good care of it.
It served me well.
Relax, my van’s loaded.
What’s worrying you?
We’ll make the shipment on time.
Gotta go.
You’re all set, brother.
Nice job.
That’s thick!
That’s the spice.
Fuck you, fucker!
So, once there was a boat.
It didn’t belong to anyone.
At the same time,
it belonged to everyone.
It caught a lot of fish
for the village.
Eventually, the boat needed
to be retired.
They kept it in the village square,
like a monument.
Over time, this boat was falling apart.
They replaced each broken piece
with a new one.
Made it strong.
By the end,
every single piece had been
replaced.
Now, if you change
every piece of a boat...
Is it still the same boat?
And if not...
What does it become?
What’s up?
Nothing.
Can I meet you at home?
Nothing’s biting today.
Nothing’s biting!
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull